thekooza.com 2016-09-23

# The Kooza privacy policy |

**Privacy policy**

This is the foremost privacy policy for The Kooza.com and The Kooza Media Group publications online, and for specific services given by the websites by The Kooza Media Group

At The Kooza.com we gather diverse kinds of information regarding our users for four main reasons:

To give personalized services exclusive to individual users.

To assist us to monitor and perk up the services we propose

To sell advertising space on the site. This assists us to keep the site free of charge.

With user permission, to market services to individuals’ users.

There can be further privacy policies that give to particular services on The Kooza.com

Please read these at the time you register or subscribe for these services on these sites.

Please pursue the links below for more details.

**Our principles**

We perform our best to guard user privacy by the suitable use of the security technology.

This means: - we make sure that we have proper physical and technological security measures to secure your information - we make sure that when we outsource any procedures that the service supplier has proper security measures.

We will value your privacy. You should get marketing emails just from DMG and, if you select, from cautiously selected third parties.

It will be made obvious to you where you have these options; for instance, tick boxes will let you choose whether you wish to get marketing.

We can, though, email you infrequently with information or questions regarding your registration, your subscription account or postings, for instance, with reminders, warnings or copyright requests.

We will gather and employ individual user information merely where we have legal business causes and are legally named to do so.

We will be obvious in our dealings with you as to what information regarding we will gather and how we will employ your information.

We will employ personal data merely for the reason(s) for which they were originally gathered and we will make sure personal data are strongly disposed of.

Our site is available by the Internet. This illustrates that, wherever you opt to post your data on the site, they can be evaluated from anywhere across the globe.

**How we use your information**

**What information do we gather?        **

We gather details on our users by registration and use of the website, by cookies, where you opt to reveal data in postings, and when you go into sales promotions and competitions (“sales promotions”).

Specific services that we give can include the compilation by us of further information, for example, your geographic position from time to time, to allow the service to be given as designed. Especially, this can apply to specific Apps that you download, or which we give.

**Registration**

The least information we require to register a user is an email address and a password. We will inquire more questions for diverse services, involving sales promotions. Unless said all registration inquiries are obligatory.

We can also inquire a few additional, voluntary queries throughout registration for specific services (for instance, Classifieds, or Registration for Events) so we can get a clearer consideration of our users. This also makes us capable of personalizing services for our users.

**Logging in employing social networking credentials**

If you log in to The Kooza.com using a Facebook login as a means of authentication you grant consent to Facebook to share your user information. This will involve your name, email address, date of birth and position which will then be employed to form a KOOZA USER, and you can use your image from Facebook as part of your profile. Authenticating also authorizes the sharing of your gender, networks, user ID and any further details you opt to share according to your Facebook account settings. If you eliminate The Kooza app from your Facebook settings, our availability to this further information will stop.

If you log in to The Kooza.com using a twitter login as a means of authentication we get your avatar and twitter username.

**Use of children’s data**

Apart from Young World, The Kooza.com does not deliberately gather or store any personal information regarding children under the age of 16.

Young World online is a service for kids, which needs parental approval to join, no personal details on kids are showcased on the site, and all contributions are moderated before being cited.

**Who we share data with**

We will not share your personal information with others for marketing aims unless you have provided us your consent. With your consent, we will share your details just with cautiously selected third parties.

DMG can make obtainable third party services; any information, which is gathered by DMG when you access a third party service, is a procedure under this Privacy Policy. Information gathered by third party operators themselves is ruled by their own privacy policies.

Be careful that we set aside the right to access and reveal personal data to obey with appropriate laws and lawful government requests, to function our systems correctly and to defend both our users and ourselves.

Any third parties who access your data in the course of giving services on our behalf are a matter to firm contractual restrictions to make sure that your data is secured and in compliance with appropriate data protection/privacy legislation. We can also separately audit these service suppliers to make sure that they meet our standards. We can employ service suppliers to assist us to run these site or services available on the sites, some of which can be based outside of Pakistan.

Some DMG WebPages use plugins from third party platforms (for example the ‘Facebook Recommend’ function). These third party suppliers can gather information regarding your visit to DMG websites on these pages. If you browse these pages at the same time as still also logged in to your account on the third party platform, information gathered by the third party may be linked to your account on the third party platform. For further details on how these third parties employ information, please read their privacy policies.

**Use of Cookies**

We employ cookies for a number of causes:

For statistical aims to track how many individual exclusive users we have and how often they visit our websites. We gather data listing which of our pages are most often visited and by which types of users and from which countries.

We employ third parties to gather unidentified user details, sometimes by cookies and web beacons. Click here to learn more about how we use a third party service to gather and employ information on The Kooza.com

DMG and third party advertisers will produce statistical cookies to track advertising impressions and conversions.

Placing cookies on your computer mean we can serve you adverts that you might be much interested in, and permit us to control the number of times you see them and gauge how effectual the ad campaign has been. This assists us to keep the site free of charge.

Flash cookies can be employed to store user preferences for media player functionality and without them, some video content may not render correctly. You can turn cookies off but if you do this you cannot be capable of using all services on our websites and you might see more pop-ups and other intrusive advertising as we won’t be able to limit what you see using cookies. You will, however, still be able to view editorial content.

For more information about cookies and managing those, including how to turn them off, please visit our page on Cookies.

By employing the sites you are agreeing to the use of cookies as described.

**About our advertising**

We use targeted advertising, which permits us to convey visitors to our website directed to your interests. As you browse The Kooza.com, a few of the cookies we put on your computer will be advertising cookies, so we can recognize what sort of pages you are concerned. This details we gather regarding behavior on your computer allows us to group it with computers that illustrate similar behavior. We can then show advertising to your computer, which is based on these interests. For example, if you have been reading a lot of food and drink articles we may decide to illustrate you many adverts for food and drink. We do not share behavioral data with other websites.

**Other Advertising**

The Kooza.com will hold related associate connections from which we may gross income. Advertisers or associates never influence our articles, nor are they written for the aim of promoting a product, apart from when evidently branded as a ‘sponsored feature’ or ‘advertisement feature’ or ‘sponsor’s content’.

**Legal information and how to contact us**

If you would like to get a copy of the personal data we give you or have any questions about DMG use of personal data please contact the Data Protection Manager.

**Changes to the privacy policy**

Should we select to alter our privacy policy we will post the alterations here. Where the alterations are important, we can also opt to email all our registered employers with the new details. Where needed by law, will we get your permission to make these alterations?
